

- linnhtetaung2222@gmail.com
- **\** +95 9409333550
- Kunchan 1st Street, Kamayut Township, Yangon

# Skills

Sketch

Illustrations

Character Development

Logo and Branding

**Animation** 

## **Tools**

Photoshop

Illustrator

**Procreate** 

Blender

<u>LinkedIn</u>	7
<u>Gmail</u>	<b>(7)</b>
Portfolio Portfolio	(7)

#### About me

Experienced freelance visual designer boasting over six years of expertise, with a focus on sketching, illustration, logo and mascot design, branding, and animations. Driven by innovation and a passion for creativity, I am eager to collaborate on exciting and challenging programming projects.

# Experience

#### iMyanmarHouse Co., Ltd.

Dec 2021 - Mar 2023

- NFT illustration for 2 websites
- Created alien NFT characters
- Illustrated storyboard
- Developed Mascot characters
- Created posters for special occasions and holidays throughout calendar year

### Freelance Visual Designer

Apr 2018 - Present

- · Traditional drawing and sketches
- Portrait illustrations
- Cartoon illustrations
- · Logo designs and branding
- Character drawing
- Tattoo illustration
- 2D animations

## Education

### **Bachelor of Information Technology**

Dec 2014 - Mar 2022

West Yangon Technological University

# Other Experiences

## **UI/UX** Designer

iMyanmarHouse, Lota Global, Global Wave Technology